<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Agricare</title>
	<atom:link href="https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/category/technology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare</link>
	<description>Best Agric Extension Service in Ghana</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 18:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/agric.jpeg</url>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Agricare</title>
	<link>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Technology My Friend as a Farmer</title>
		<link>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/technology-my-friend-as-a-farmer/</link>
					<comments>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/technology-my-friend-as-a-farmer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 18:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Farmer's Hand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Our Service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Farmer My Friend]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/?p=339</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Understanding the potential applications of Artificial Intelligence in Agriculture Sector: Highlights In recent years, Artificial Intelligence (AI) has been extensively applied in farming. AI helps farmers choose the optimum seed for a given weather scenario. AI-powered solutions will help farmers produce more with lesser resources and improve crop quality. Significant applications of AI in agriculture...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><span class="title-text">Understanding the potential applications of Artifici</span><span class="title-text">al Intelligence in Agriculture Sector:</span></h1>
<h2>Highlights</h2>
<div id="abssec0020">
<div id="abspara0020" class="u-margin-s-bottom">
<ul>
<li id="p0010" class="u-margin-s-bottom">In recent years, Artificial Intelligence (AI) has been extensively applied in farming.</li>
</ul>
<ul class="list">
<li class="react-xocs-list-item">
<div id="p0015" class="u-margin-s-bottom">AI helps farmers choose the optimum seed for a given weather scenario.</div>
</li>
<li class="react-xocs-list-item">
<div id="p0020" class="u-margin-s-bottom">AI-powered solutions will help farmers produce more with lesser resources and improve crop quality.</div>
</li>
<li class="react-xocs-list-item">
<div id="p0025" class="u-margin-s-bottom">
<p>Significant applications of AI in agriculture are identified and discussed.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-68 " src="https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/team1.jpeg" alt="service image" width="758" height="571" /></p>
<h3 class="section-title u-h4 u-margin-l-top u-margin-xs-bottom">Abstract</h3>
<div id="abssec0010">
<div id="abspara0010" class="u-margin-s-bottom">Artificial Intelligence (AI) has been extensively applied in farming recently. To cultivate healthier crops, manage pests, monitor soil and growing conditions, analyse data for farmers, and enhance other management activities of the food supply chain, the <a class="topic-link" title="Learn more about agriculture from ScienceDirect's AI-generated Topic Pages" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/agricultural-science">agriculture</a> sector is turning to AI technology. It makes it challenging for farmers to choose the ideal time to <a class="topic-link" title="Learn more about plant seeds from ScienceDirect's AI-generated Topic Pages" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/spermatophyte">plant seeds</a>. AI helps farmers choose the optimum seed for a particular weather scenario. It also offers data on <a class="topic-link" title="Learn more about weather forecasts from ScienceDirect's AI-generated Topic Pages" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/earth-and-planetary-sciences/weather-forecast">weather forecasts</a>. AI-powered solutions will help farmers produce more with fewer resources, increase crop quality, and hasten product time to reach the market. AI aids in understanding soil qualities. AI helps farmers by suggesting the nutrients they should apply to increase the quality of the soil. AI can help farmers choose the optimal time to plant their seeds. Intelligent equipment can calculate the spacing between seeds and the maximum planting depth. An AI-powered system known as a health monitoring system provides farmers with information on the health of their crops and the nutrients that need to be given to enhance yield quality and quantity. This study identifies and analyses relevant articles on AI for Agriculture. Using AI, farmers can now access advanced data and analytics tools that will foster better farming, improve efficiencies, and reduce waste in biofuel and <a class="topic-link" title="Learn more about food production from ScienceDirect's AI-generated Topic Pages" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/earth-and-planetary-sciences/food-production">food production</a> while minimising the negative environmental impacts. AI and Machine Learning (ML) have transformed various industries, and the AI wave has now reached the agriculture sector. Companies are developing several technologies to make monitoring farmers&#8217; crop and soil health easier. <a class="topic-link" title="Learn more about Hyperspectral imaging from ScienceDirect's AI-generated Topic Pages" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/earth-and-planetary-sciences/hyperspectral-imaging">Hyperspectral imaging</a> and 3D laser scanning are the leading AI-based technologies that can help ensure crop health. These AI-powered technologies collect precise data on the health of the crops in greater volume for analysis. This paper studied AI and its need in Agriculture. The process of AI in Agriculture and some Agriculture parameters monitored by AI are briefed. Finally, we identified and discussed the significant applications of AI in agriculture.</div>
</div>
</div>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/technology-my-friend-as-a-farmer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best 6 Pests and Diseases Control</title>
		<link>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/best-6-pests-and-diseases-control/</link>
					<comments>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/best-6-pests-and-diseases-control/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 07:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Our Service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advance Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expert Advise]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/?p=335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Integrated pest management 1 What is IPM? For each pest and disease covered in this manual, methods are ﬁrst given for prevention of the problem. Then, if intervention is needed when a pest or disease occurs, the safest and most effective options available are listed. The approach used in the manual is called Integrated Pest...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 class="t m0 x5 ha y34 ff1 fs6 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0"><a href="https://www.agrifarming.in/"><strong>Integrated pest management</strong></a></h1>
<h2 class="t m0 x5 h7 y91 ff1 fs4 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">1 What is IPM?</h2>
<div class="t m0 x5 h9 y92 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">For each pest and disease covered in this manual, methods are ﬁrst given for prevention of the problem. Then, if intervention is needed when a pest or disease occurs, the safest and most effective options available are listed.</div>
<div><img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-120 " src="https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ext1-1.jpeg" alt="" width="736" height="402" /></div>
<div></div>
<div class="t m0 x5 h9 y94 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">The approach used in the manual is called Integrated Pest Management (IPM).</div>
<div class="t m0 x5 h9 y95 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">IPM consists of 4 main steps:</div>
<div></div>
<ul>
<li class="t m0 x5 h9 y96 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">1. Identiﬁcation: The section on <span class="ff3">Key Signs</span> is designed to help identify the pest or disease.</li>
<li class="t m0 x5 h9 y97 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">2. Prevention: This includes cultural approaches, such as use of disease resistant varieties, disease-free seed and</li>
<li class="t m0 x8 h9 y98 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">adoption of good practices in the ﬁeld, such as removal of infected material that could carry the problem over to</li>
<li class="t m0 x8 h9 y99 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">the next crop. It also includes use of pesticides where this method is appropriate.</li>
<li class="t m0 x5 h9 y9a ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">3. Monitoring: The earlier a pest or disease is noticed, the earlier appropriate action can be taken to reduce losses</li>
<li class="t m0 x8 h9 y9b ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">and prevent its spread.</li>
<li class="t m0 x5 h9 y9c ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">4. Control: This includes both cultural approaches, such as removal of infected plants, as well as use of appropriate</li>
<li class="t m0 x8 h9 y9d ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0">pesticides.</li>
</ul>
<div class="t m0 x5 h9 y9e ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">IPM often involves the combination of several different options. Pesticides tend to be used when other approaches are</div>
<div class="t m0 x5 h9 y9f ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">inadequate for the problem at hand; they must always be used in accordance with the usage and safety information</div>
<div class="t m0 x5 h9 ya0 ff2 fs5 fc2 sc0 ls0 ws0">given on the pack.</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://elvis9321.github.io/agricare/best-6-pests-and-diseases-control/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
